WSYR Collection
WSYR Collection
- Audiorecordings
  - Woman’s World: Abraham Lincoln Portrait in Sound, Kay Russell, 02/12/1973; wsyr_radio_919; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 11:16 (Box 52)
  - Woman’s World: Lincoln Program, with Kay Russell, 02/12/1975; wsyr_radio_917; routine sheet included in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 6:45 (Box 51)
  - Woman’s World: Shoplifting Interview, 12/26/1972; 01/02/1973; wsyr_radio_961; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 55)
  - Woman’s World: Urban Improvement Panel Discussion - Ladies Day, 10/08/1976; 10/13/1976; wsyr_radio_913; guests: John Searles, Elliott Jacobson, Jerry Wilson, Erwin Shultz, mediator: Kay Russell; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 21:15 (Box 51)
  - WSYR - "Weekend World" - Collector’s Corner Programs - Charles Hobart, host - Collector’s Corner. (Reel 1), wsyr_radio_447; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 59:18 (Box 9)
  - WSYR - "Weekend World" - Collector’s Corner Programs - Charles Hobart, host - Collectors Corner (Reel 3), wsyr_radio_449; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 64:21 (Box 10)
  - WSYR - "Weekend World" - Collector’s Corner Programs - Charles Hobart, host (Reel 2), wsyr_radio_448; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 65:23 (Box 9)
  - WSYR - "Weekend World" - Collector’s Corner Programs - Charles Hobart, host (Reel 4), wsyr_radio_450; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 64:21 (Box 10)
  - WSYR - "Weekend World" - Collector’s Corner Programs - Charles Hobart, host (Reel 5), wsyr_radio_451; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 48:21 (Box 10)
  - WSYR - Australian Almanac, wsyr_radio_564; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
    1 - Australian Aboriginal Dance Troupe; 2 - African Drum Collection; 3 - Wresting Away the America’s Cup (Yachting); 4 - Visit to Magpie Theatre; 5 - Commonwealth Heads of Gov’t. Meeting in Melbourne.
  - WSYR - Australian Almanac, wsyr_radio_565; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 20)
    1 - Australian Film Maker; 2 - Host Family Service; 3 - Aboriginal dialects; 4 - Pres. of International Assembly of Sports Confederations; 5 - American poet living in Australia.
  - WSYR - Australian Almanac, May 1981; wsyr_radio_566; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:00 (Box 21)
    "This program is sent to you through the courtesy of the Australian Information Service. it is compiled and edited by Gerry Hughes, an Australian broadcaster." 1 - Click Go The Shears - Sheep Shearing Song; 2 - Origins of Australian people; 3 - The Outback - Armed Forces Food Sciences; 4 - Flying instructor Linda Bishop.
  - WSYR - Australian Almanac, 06/11/1981; wsyr_radio_567; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 23:10 (Box 21)
    "This program is sent to you through the courtesy of the Australian Information Service. it is compiled and edited by Gerry Hughes, an Australian broadcaster." 1 - Research about "The Family Doctor"; 2 - How memory works; 3 - Musician who plays beer cartons.
  - WSYR - Early News, Air check, 09/23/1972; wsyr_radio_981; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 56)
  - WSYR - George Roberts Show - (part 3, number 2), 02/03/1974; wsyr_radio_502; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 16)
  - WSYR - George Roberts Show (part 3, number 3), 02/16/1974; wsyr_radio_503; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 16)
  - WSYR - Mutual Radio Network - 1976 Year In Review, 01/01/1977; wsyr_radio_473; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - WSYR - President Nixon - Phase 2 of Economic Program, 10/07/1971; wsyr_radio_489; includes fragment of NBC News On The Hour; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - WSYR - Swearing In of Gerald Ford as Vice President; News + Views: Black Perspective (fragment), 02/11/1973; 12/06/1973; wsyr_radio_500; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 16)
    Levels increas after first minute (+, -) After Agnew Resigns...; Interview - Dennis Dowdell fragment - 2/11/73 Sh. #77 "News + Views - Black Perspective" tv. sound track.
  - WSYR - Syracuse - Civil Disorders (part 2) air check, 8/17-18 [1967]; wsyr_radio_482; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - WSYR - Syracuse - Racial Disturbances (part 1) air check, 8/16-17, 1967; wsyr_radio_481; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - WSYR - Windjammer Master #3, wsyr_radio_457; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 31:00 (Box 11)
  - WSYR 40th Anniversary Show - Protection Copy - 1922-1962, wsyr_radio_461; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 59:09 (Box 11)
  - WSYR 50th Anniversary Program, 1972; wsyr_radio_491; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - WSYR AM - 50th Anniversary Program, 1972; wsyr_radio_470; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - WSYR FM Broadcast "Stereo" 1964; "Alan Milair Show", wsyr_radio_462; FM Stereo Introduction from 1962; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - WSYR New Horizon Interview from London (part 1 of 2), 07/06/1946; wsyr_radio_310; This is The Radio Workshop of Syracuse University recording, disc #2726, order # 1279 of a WSYR program; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - WSYR New Horizon Interview from London (part 2 of 2), 07/06/1946; wsyr_radio_311; This is The Radio Workshop of Syracuse University recording, disc #2727, order # 1279 of a WSYR program.; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - WSYR Special FM Stereo Checkout Program, 1964; wsyr_radio_479; Alan Milair, Host; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
  - WSYR tidbits and Baseball Game - Yogi Berra. World Series Game delayed by rain, John Gray Show (fragment), wsyr_radio_542; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 19)
  - WSYR Weekend World - Educational Broadcasting Course: Onondaga Community College Features, 04/12/1975; 04/13/1975; 04/19/1975; 04/20/1975; 04/26/1975; 04/27/1975; 05/03/1975; 05/10/1975; wsyr_radio_921; note reads "All features were aired 5-6 PM on date indicated, all features run approximately 5:55"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 47:33 (Box 52)
    Girl Going West, Aired: April 12, 1975; Depression, Aired: April 13, 1975; ‘20’s Bar, Aired: April, 19, 1975; Nazi Germany - 1935, Aired: April 20, 1975; 1900’s Housewife, Aired: April 26, 1975; Lincoln’s Aide, Aired: April 27, 1975; Custer’s Scout, Aired: May 3, 1975; Civil War, Aired: May 10, 1975
  - WSYR-AM On Air programming, 09/17/1979; wsyr_radio_474; Sign-on Saturday 9/15/79 Thru Sign-off Monday 9/17/79.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 13)
  - WSYR-AM: The Unexplained, No 101-127 (Master tape 1), Nov 1979; wsyr_radio_948; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 54)
    101: Why They Return; 102: Houdini’s Message; 103: Ghost of War; 104: No Grass on the Grave; 105: Selfpreservation; 106: Music Box Ghost; 107: Wall beneath the Waves; 108: Firewalking; 109: Missile Mile; 110: Dreams that came true; 111: The Hanging Tree; 112: Animals life savers; 113: ESP Projection; 114: Danine Clarvoyants [?]; 115: Desert Mystery; 116: Mand’ with the X-Ray Mind; 117: A Patch of Rainfall; 118: Water Dowsing; 119: Dreams that Paid Off; 120: ESP and Plants; 121: The Screaming Mummy; 122: Boy with the Healing Fingers; 123: The Yellow Balloons; 124: The Warning Canary; 125: Bowels of the Earth; 126: The Flying Monk; 127: Elecyro-Photography [sic]
  - WSYR-AM: The Unexplained, No 128-153 (Master tape 2), Nov 1979; wsyr_radio_949; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 54)
    128: The Troubled Palomino; 129: Healing Thru Mind Power; 130: The Midnight Knocking; 131: Fraud-Buster Houdini; 132: Ringing Bells - English Setter; 133: The Missing Fingers; 134: The Death Bobbins; 135: Rocks from the Sky; 136: Mental Photography; 137: Headless Brakeman; 138: Levitation in 1860; 139: Mountain Flyer’s Message; 140: The Power of Suggestion; 141: ESP of Cats; 142: Beeps in the Night; 143: A Life-saving Vision; 144: Fantastic Fotos; 145: Night-time Dream Trip; 146: Dream Prophecies; 147: Ghost of Octagon House; 148: Good Samaritans; 149: Apparitions; 150: More Apparitions; 151: The Six Sense in Animals; 152: The Phantom Truck; 153: The Boy Who Talked with Animals
  - WSYR-AM: The Unexplained, No 154-167 (Master tape 3), Nov 1979; wsyr_radio_950; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 54)
    154: The Bank Street Ghost; 155: Another UFO Riffle; 156: The Giant Compass; 157: Eileen Garnett’s ESP; 158: Eyeless Sight; 159: Myster [sic] of the Midnight Watch; 160: Lost Knowledge of History; 161: Wreck of the Princess Alice; 162: Bread Upon the Waters; 163: Lodgings for the Night; 164: Roof-top Poltergeist; 165: Uncanny Letters of Edgar Morris; 166: Tea-cup Television; 167: The Woodpecker Mystery
  - WSYR-TV News Intros and Outtros, wsyr_radio_005; side A - 4 intros, cut 4 used. side B - 4 outtros, cut 4 used. sponsor - Piels Light Beer. a note on the record reads: "WSYR-TV News outtros and intros with voiceovers."; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1: "WSYR-TV News Intros"; Side 2: "WSYR-TV News Outtros"
  - WSYR-TV-FM - Loew’s State Theatre documentary, 11/19/1978; wsyr_radio_475; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 14)
    1 - Raising Of WSYR-TV Antenna (Feb. 1, 1950); 2 - Inaugural Broadcast of WSYR-FM (July 9, 1946); 3 - "The Palace On Salina Street" - Loew’s State Theatre (Nov. 19, 1978)
  - WSYR-TV: Contest Congress, Ford Hillegas [?], moderator, 09/22/1968; 09/23/1968; wsyr_radio_952; note on box reads "Recorded WSYR-TV taping session 2:00 PM, Sunday September 22, 1968. For Broadcast Monday 09/23/1968. Return to: Dr. Daver"; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 29:10 (Box 54)
  - WSYR-TV: Ladies Day: Interview with Jane Fonda, Kay Russell and Fred Hilbgas, interviewing (9-9:30 AM), 10/10/1972; wsyr_radio_915; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 51)
  - WSYR-TV: P. E. A. C. E. Interview on Ladies Day TV Program (at 9:22 AM), 04/10/1973; wsyr_radio_911; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 51)
  - WSYR, University College Special Program: Gourmet Cooking, 06/10/1980; 06/15/1980; wsyr_radio_712; host Dr. Robert Cecile, and guest Gordon Symonds; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 54:18 (Box 36)
  - WSYR, University College Special Program: Syracuse Stage, 04/22/1980; 04/25/1980; 06/22/1980; wsyr_radio_711; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - WSYR, University College: Solar Energy, 07/05/1979; 07/29/1979; 08/12/1979; 01/27/1980; wsyr_radio_710; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 54:05 (Box 36)
  - WSYR: Dr. Calvin M. Thompson, Memorial Broadcast, wsyr_radio_958; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 55)
  - WSYR: The Love Makers (parts 1 & 2), wsyr_radio_709; note on label reads HEADS; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 36)
  - WSYR/NBC Tidbits - Monitor Radio, 1969; wsyr_radio_485; assortment: Ottoway to news to baseball to monitor; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 15)
  - Yankees, 04/06/1982; 04/14/1982; wsyr_radio_623; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
- Files
  - Advertiser log, local, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Advertiser logs, local and national, 1945; 2 volumes (Box 1)
  - Advertiser logs, local and national, 1946; 2 volumes (Box 1)
  - Advertiser logs, local and national, 1947; 2 volumes (Box 1)
  - Advertiser logs, local and national, 1948; 2 volumes (Box 1)
  - Advertiser logs, local and national, 1949; 2 volumes (Box 1)
  - Advertiser logs, local and national, 1950; 2 volumes (Box 1)
  - Advertiser log, national, 1951 (Box 1)
  - Advertiser log, national, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Advertiser log, national, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Broadcast notes, 1933-1938; 4 folders (Box 2)
  - Broadcast notes, 1939-1942; 5 folders (Box 3)
  - Broadcast notes, 1943-1946; 5 folders (Box 4)
  - Broadcast notes, 1947-1952 Jun; 6 folders (Box 5)
  - Broadcast notes, 1952 Jul-1956; 5 foldes (Box 6)
  - Broadcast notes, 1957-1961; 5 folders (Box 7)
  - Milair personal, 1967-1974; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - NBC Radio Network Operations Manual, Jul 1975 (Box 8)
  - Newhouse dinner and dedication, May 1974 (Box 8)
  - Pres. Richard Nixon - Frost interviews, May 1977; includes photograph of Nixon and Frost (Box 8)
  - Press kit, Mutual Black Network (Box 8)
  - Press kits, WSYR (Box 8)
  - Printed material, miscellaneous (Box 8)
  - Programs, "Concert Hall" (incomplete), 1960-1967; 5 folders (Box 8)
  - "A Quarter of a Century at the Crossroads", 1959; compilation of philosophical/spiritual remarks by Dr. Calvin M. Thompson Jr. during his 25 years as host of WSYR's "Meeting at the Crossroads"; forward by E. R. Vadeboncoeur, president of WSYR (Box 8)
  - Rural guide and compass system map of Cortland County, 1940 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8)